Guide to the W. W. Morgan Papers circa 1905-1990
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Research
  - Subseries 2: Graphic Documents
    - Observation cards, "Perseus Clusters I", "O and B Stars: Including those Observed by Stebbius, Huffer, and Whitford for Color, the OB Stars from the Cleveland Program, and the HD O and B Stars Fainter than 5.50 and North of -20°, 19h", "Dwarfs of uknown Spectral Type", "c Stars of Classes B and A", "Standard Stars within 10 PC", "C-Stars F0 - K5", "Selected High Velocitiy Stars", "Standard Stars", "Members of the Cora Bereni Cluster", undated (Box 70)
    - Observation cards, "Wolf-Rayet Stars", "Variable Stars", "M0, M1, M2 Dwarf Stars", ""M" Stars", "Hyades Cluster", "Red Variables Having Ranges less than 2 mag. and Visual Minima Brighter than 10.0", "O-Stars", "Cepheid Variables, Gaposchkin - Variable Stars", undated (Box 71)
    - Orion Cluster, Folder 1, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Orion Cluster, Folder 2, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Papers, Illustrations for Morgan-Walboro-Tabscott, undated (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Perseus, Cluster, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Photographic and Star Charts, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Plate A Madison, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Pleione, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Seyfert Galaxy Paper Prints, 1967 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Spectra, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Spectral Classification Unknowns (original), undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Spectral Unknowns, 1964-1966 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Star Field Maps, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Star Tables, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Studies in Spectral Classification III: Monoceros, 1965 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Supergiants 09-B8, undated (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Toronto Paper: Best Set, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Toronto Paper: Final Prints, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Transparencies, undated (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Transparencies for Chicago Colloquium, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Unknown, 1964-1968 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Unknown 21-32, Jan. 23, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Unknown Prints (Last Batch), Folder 1, undated (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Unknown Prints (Last Batch), Folder 2, undated (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Wide-Angle Prints from Code, undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - VII Cygni, undated (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - ζ Oph HII Region, undated (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Alpha Ovitail Prints, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Alpha Persei, Cluster Illustrations, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 200-inch Prints from Plate of M31, 1951 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3: Tables and Calculations
    - Abell Cluster on Palomar Prints, undated (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - ABT Binary Spectra, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Abt, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Abt, Bless, Morgan, Far W Classification, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Atlas, B5-F5, undated (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Atlas Charts, undated (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Atlas, F8-G0, undated (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Atlas, F8-K2, undated (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Atlas, G-K, undated (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Basel Stars, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Basel O-B Stars, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - B-Stars, undated (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Charts, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Charts, A0-F0,undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Charts, F2-G2,undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Counts of G5-K5 Stars 5.5-6.5, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Deep Region, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Deutsch Plates, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Eggen B9 - A2, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Faint Standard Fields, undated (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Galactic Forms Table, undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Garrison Four-Color, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - gK0 - gK5 & K0 III - K5 III; K0 II-III - K5 II-III; K0 III-IV - K5 III-IV, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Globular Clusters and Photometric Data, undated (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - G5-K5 Stars, undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Harris - K Plates, undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Harris Plates, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Hyades, undated (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Late-Type Emission-Line Stars, undated (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - List of Standard Stars Illustrated in MAT Atlas, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Luminosity Effects at BO, undated (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Luminosity Effects at G2, undated (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Madison Group Work, undated (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Derck Massa, 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - MAT - Continuing Work, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Mathematical Tables, undated (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - MK Revised Standards, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Morgan-Neff, April, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Nikonov - B8-B9 Stars, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Notebooks, Double Entry, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Orion, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Orion B. Group, undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Orion Variables, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - O-Stars - Atlas, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Palomar Plate Tables, undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Papers, 1981-1982 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Papers, n.d (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Papers, undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Photometric, Polarization, and Spectrographic Observations of O-Stars, Hiltner, 1956-1969 10 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Photometry Tables, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Plates Borrowed, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - PSS, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Revised Frame of Reference F8-K3, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - SC/C Cluster - Beritau, undated (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Schild Standards, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Second Yerkes Atlas, Mount Wilson Spectra, undated (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Southern B-Stars, undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Spectral Unknowns, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Strong Standards, 1986-1988 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Subdwarfs, undated (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Tables, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Tables, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Tables, undated (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Tables, undated (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Tables, January 3 - March 14, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - TMK Tables, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Unknowns, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Unknowns Class, Fall, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Unknowns: Spectral Classification, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Ursa Major, Cloud, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Variable Stars: Classes R and N, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Virgo Cluster, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Walborn Tables, undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - The Wolf Rayet Stars, undated (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - X Plates A0-F5, undated (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - X Plates F0-K5, undated (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - 22 Cygni Region, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 4: Research and Scholarly Papers
    - Abt Helmut A., Folder 1, 1982-1987 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Abt Helmut A., Folder 2, 1981-1982 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Albert Elise, 1975-1982 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Abell, Stellar Evolution Diagrams, undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Astrophysical Journal, An Investigation of Stellar Motions, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Austin Papers, 1962-1963 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Bahcall, Neta A. "Clusters of Galaxies," 1976 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Blaauw/Johnson Vol. 3 Kuiper, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Bok Bart J., "Photo Electric Colors of B Stars in Five Regions of the Southern Milky Way", undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - cD Cluster Reprints, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Chandrasekhar Relativity Reprints, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Correction, in Km per sec., to Radial Velocity due to Earth's Rotation for Yerkes Observatory, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Crawford Measures, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Fujita's Note on Classification of Red Carbon Stars, undated (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Galactic Structure, 1973-1981 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Gallagher-Wirth, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Garrison, Robert F., 1977-1988 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Heckmann - Lubeck, Hyades, 1956-1964 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Hopkins Jeanne, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Hubble Constant Series, Papers I, II, IV, and V, Left by Allan Sandage, 1973-1974 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - IC 4665, 1964-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Intrinsic Colors; Zaris Johnson, BHD, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - IZw Objects - Not on Sargent's List; IZw Objects on Sargent's List+ II Zw1, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Jenner David C., "Supergiant Galaxies with Multiple Nuclei," 1974 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Johnson Harold L., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Johnson Harold L., 1976 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Johnson-Hiltner Calibration, ApJ 123, 267, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Jones Burton F.: Faint Pleiades, 1972 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Kayser Susan, 1962-1973 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Keenan, Philip C., "1985 Revised Mk Spectral Standards: Stars Go and Later," 1985 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Keenan Calibration, B.A.D., 1963 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Kennedy, Pamela Morris, "Interstellar Line Velocities in the Southern Milky Way," 1966 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Kron Richard G., 1981-1985 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Lola Judy, 1979-1982 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Luyten: Stars of v.v. Low Luminosity, 1974 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Marschall Thesis, "High Resolution Studies of the Interstellar Calcium Lines," 1971 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Mendoza: Pleiades, Hz II Pleiades; Kraft: v sin i Pleiades, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Mendoza, "A Spectroscopic Study of the Pleiades," 1955 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Mihalas Dimitri, Longair I.A.U. Paper, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Mihalas Dimitri, "On the Relevance of the mK System and process to the theory of stellar atomospheres", 1983 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Mihalas Dimitri, Paper, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Mihalas Dimitri, Toronto Manuscript, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Mihalas Dimitri, Toronto Manuscript, Master Copy 19884 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Molnar: AP Stars, 1974-1978 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Moore J.H., "Fifth Catalog of the Orbital Elements of Spetroscopic Binary Stars", 1949 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Neff John, Spectroscopic Study of the Andromeda Nebula", 1963 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Neff John, Calibration of Sensitive Functions, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - NGC 752, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Ostriker J.P. and Gunn J.E. "On The Nature of Pulsars: III. Analysis of Observations", Manuscripts, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Palmer, 1968-1972 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Ramsey Paper, undated (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Revised Atlas Work Books, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Roman Nancy, "The Ursa Major Group," undated (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Rybski Paul, Folder 1, 1984-1987 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Rybski Paul, Folder 2, 1983-1984 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Rybski Paul, Folder 3, 1982-1983 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 1, OB Stars, 1955-1974 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 2, Photometry Papers 1961-1974 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 3, 1936-1978 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 4, 1974-1978 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 5, 1971-1978 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 6, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 7, 1972-1974 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 8, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 9, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Scholarly Papers, Folder 10, 1932-1979 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Segal I.E., Articles, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Segal I.E., Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Superclusters, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - The Observatory: A Review of Astronomy, Number One Thousand, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - van Altena William F., "Astrometry," undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - van Altena William F., NSF AST 76-81339, Oct 29, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - van den Bergh Sidney. Clusters of Galaxies, undated (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Walborn, Atlas, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Walborn: Final Version Supplement Summary, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Walborn: N-C Stars, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Walborn: Nitrogen Anomaly, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Walborn, "On the Existence of OB Stars with Anomalous Nitrogen and Carbon Spectra," undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Walborn: η Car, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Walborn: η Car, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Walborn, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Withford A.E., Six-Color Photometery: Paper on 238 Stars, 1945 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - R. R. Zappala, Classification of Criteria F8-K5, undated (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - 84" Image Intensifier Sample Photograph, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - γ Vel, Abt, Landolt, 1958-1970 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 5: Publications
    - Abt-Morgan-Garrison II, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - "Apparent Variation of Intensity of Lines of HeI in the Spectrum of B7III-B9III", Abt Helmut, Morgan W.W., 1981 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - "The Application of the Principle of Natural Groups to the Classification of Stellar Spectra", undated (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Articles, 1931-1986 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Atlas of Stellar Spectra, Introduction, Draft, 1967 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Atlas of Stellar Spectra, Revised Standards, 1964-965 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Bautz-Morgan, Folder 1, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Bautz-Morgan, Folder 2, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Bautz-Morgan, "On the Classification of the Form of Clusters of Galaxies", Master Copy, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Bautz-Morgan, "On the Classification of the Form of Clusters of Galaxies", Xerox and Carbon, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Bibliography of W.W. Morgan, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Bibliography of W.W. Morgan, 1976-1981 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - CD Galaxy Paper, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - CD Galaxy Paper, Master, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - "The Classification of the Am Stars", 1972 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - "Classification of Compact Objects: QSS, QSO'S, N-TYPE and Compact Galaxies, Seyfert and Galactic Nuclei", 1970 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - "A Comparision of the Optical Forms of Certain Seyfert Galaxies with N-Type Radio Galaxies", 1967 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Current Investigation, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Current Research, February, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Current Research, Spectral Classification, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Dimensionless Morphologies, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - "A Discussion of Galaxies Identified with Radio Sources", Matthews Thomas and Morgan W.W.,1980-1982 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - "The Distribution of Light in the Central Regions of Some Giant Elliptical Galaxies,"Heeschen, Walborn, and Morgan, Final Manuscript, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - "On the Distribution of Interstellar Gas in the Galactic Halo", Hobbs L.M., W.W. Morgan, C.E. Albert, and Felix J. Lockman, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - "A Finding List of F Stars of High Luminosity",1952 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - "A Finding List of O an B Stars of High Luminosity", Nassau J.J. and Morgan W.W.m, 1951 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - "Flare Stars in Orion Nebula Cluster," Morgan-Haro, ApJ 118, 16, 1953 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Fragments, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Galaxies, "Collation of Optical and Radio Classification of Galaxies", 1968 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Galaxies, Clusters, Classification Scheme for Clusters of Galaxies, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Galaxies, Galaxy Forms II, "A Preliminary Classification of the Forms of Galaxies, According to their Stellar Population, II", undated (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - Green, John C. Jr., Graphic Latin, undated (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Heeschen, Walborn, Morgan, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - "The HR Diagram of the Open Cluster IC 2602," Final MS, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Hynek, "J. Allen Hynek at Yerkes Observatory: 1932-1935", 1986 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - IC 2602, Master Copy, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - IC 2602, θ Car., 1971 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts Completed or in Process, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Master Super-Supergiants, April 4, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Metallic Line Stars, 1947 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Metallic Line Stars, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - MHG: Alpha Per Master, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - MHG: Alpha Per Xerox, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Mihalas - Morgan, Chapter 1 and 2, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Mihalas - Morgan, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - MKA F Stars, Final MS, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - MKBH Revised Text, undated (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - "MK Morphology of a Group of Am Stars", with Abt Helmut, Report of Referees, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - MK System and MK Process, Master Toronto, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - M-L Star System, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Morphology of Optical Forms of N Galaxies, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - N-Galaxies, Paper, October, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - N-Galaxies, Quasars, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - NGC 2516, 1965-1969. (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - NGC 2516, 1965-1969 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - NGC 2516, undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Northwestern Paper, 1952-1953 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - NSF Proposal - 1981-1983 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - NSF Proposal, Folder 2, 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - NSF Proposal, Folder 3, 1980-1982 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - "An Optical Form Morphology of Seyfert Galaxies", 1970 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Papers, 1947-1980 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Papers, 1952-1987 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Papers, 1959-1969 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Papers, Double Stars, undated (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Pleiade, Atlas, 1943 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Proof of Presence of cD Galaxies in AWM 7 and AWM 3, 1977 1981 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Published Papers, 1946 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - References, 1958-1974 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Revised Master, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Spec. Luminosities 04-B2, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Spectral Atlas, Distribution, 1981-1989 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Spectral Atlas, Introduction to Atlas No. 2, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Spectral Atlas, Proof, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Spectral Atlas, Text Final, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Spectral Atlas, Text for Spectral Atlas (Starting with #12), 1978 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Spectral Atlas, Work in Progress, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Spectral Atlas, undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - "On the Spectroscopic Behavior of the Stars of Highest Luminosity in the Region of the Hertzsprung Gap," Morgan, Keenan, Abt, and Tapscott, undated (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Spectral Atlas, Overall Scheme, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Spectral Atlas, Plates, undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Spectral Atlas, Shipments, 1979-1980 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Spectral Atlas, Revised Spectral Atlas, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Spiral Arms (Historical), 1952-1953 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Spiral Arms, 1952-1971 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Spiral Structure, 1973-1974 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Starswith XX Plates, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Toronto Paper, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Uppsala Proof, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Vatican Paper and Atlas Typesetting, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Alpha Persei Cluster, 1968-1969 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Alpha Persei Proof, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 6: General
    - A-Stars with C1 Colors Brighter than 7.0 m, 1947 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Abt Helmut, Robert F. Garrison, Morgan W.W., Papers and Correspondence, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - An Atlas of Spectra of the Cooler Stars, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - CD Galaxies, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Classification of Clusters, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Compact Galaxies, 1964-1968 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Conti Peter, Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Developers, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Dibaj E.A., Pronik, 1971-1972 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - F Stars CII-IV, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - "Growth Rates in Various Fields of Astronomy", Abt Helmut, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Hynek Allen, Book, I Chapter, 1949 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Johnson 8-Color Bright Stars, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Keenan Philip C., "552 Stars", 1979 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Luminosity Effects At B1, undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - MAT Classification, 1980-1982 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Michigan Altlas, "Michigan Catalogue of Two-Dimensional Spectral Types for the HD Stars, Vol. II", 1974 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - The MK System and the MK Process, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Morgan Articles, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Natural Groups, undated (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Notes, "Classification of the Spectrograms", undated (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Papers, 1962 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Papers, 1974-1981 (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Prime Papers, Sigma Cas, HR 8752, 1955-1974 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Revision of 1958 of Classification of Galaxy Forms, 1958 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Schild Standards, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Spectral Classification and Threee Color Photometry of A-Type Peculiar Stars (K. Osawa), undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Stromgren 4-Color, White Review, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Tektites, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Visual Survey for Multiplicity of O-Stars, undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Wittgenstein Annotated Article, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - λ - ν Diagram, 1970 10 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Sigma Cas, HR 8752, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Sigma Cas, Creative Notes, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Sigma Cas, Etc., 1979 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Series IV: Symposia, Conferences and Workshops
  - AAS Meeting, Boulder, 1970 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - AAS Meeting, Madison, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Bengt Stromgren Symposium, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Chicago Colloquium, December 13, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Colloquia Notices, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - D.A.O. Visit, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Groningen Symposium, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Hale Observatories Visit, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - IAU, Conference, Prague, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - IAU, Symposium, Uppsala, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - IAU, Symposium, Uppsala, 1970-1971 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - IAU, Symposium, Problems of Extragalactic Research, 1960-1961 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Lausanne, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Madison Neighborhood, Midwest Astronomer Meeting, October 29, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Magnetic Clouds, Colloquium, undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Mexcio Trip, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Nassau-Morgan, Michigan Symposium, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation, Washington Trip, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - New York Symposium "Texas," 1967 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Ohio State Symposium, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - The Orion Association, Colloquium, 1961-1967 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Paris Symposium, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Pontifical Academy, Plenary Session, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Prague Travel, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Princeton Lectures, May, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Princeton Arrangements, 1968-1969 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Rome Trip, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Sandage Allan, Colloquium, Photos, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Seyfert Galaxies, Conference, Tucson, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Spectral Classification as Language, Yerkes Colloquium, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Spectroscope Colloquium, undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Stockholm Symposium, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Toronto Discussion, MK Workshop, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Toronto Papers, MK Workshop, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Toronto Papers, MK Workshop, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Tucson MS, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Tucson MS, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Tucson Trip, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Vatican, Pontifical Academy, Semaine, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Vatican, Pontifical Academy, Conferences, 1976-1978 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Washington Symposium Papers, 1976-1978 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Washington Trip, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Yerkes Colloquium, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 17)
- Series V: Administration and Organizations